B.Sc. and M.Sc. honor student in Industrial Engineering and Management within "Meitar" excellent program at Ben-Gurion University specializing in Data science. Highly motivated to engage with data analysis and integrate in the big data field. Always aiming to achieve excellence, highly self-driven, self-learner and a strong team player. Knowledgeable in Python, Java, R and MATLAB languages.

# **Education**

2020-present: **M.Sc. in Industrial Engineering and Management** (specializing in Data science) from Ben-Gurion University of the Negev.

- In my Thesis I am developing a phenotypes **prediction algorithm** based on **machine learning** using genome big data.

2017-present: **B.Sc. in Industrial Engineering and Management** (specializing in Information Systems) from Ben-Gurion University of the Negev (graduating 2021).

- GPA: 90.
- **Received Honors** in the first and second year of my studies.
- Psychometric grade: 706.

### Skills

- **Python** - **R** - SQL - Excel - **Machine Learning** 

- Java - MATLAB - PowerPoint - Word - Statistics

# **Experience**

2020-present: Teaching Assistant in "Databases" course - SQL language, Ben-Gurion University of the Negev.

2020-present: "Disco – Data Science Community (BGU)" community manager – a community established by

students with the aim of providing exposure to the field of Data Science: lectures, jobs, hackathons

and data scientist in the industry.

2019-2020: Analyst Research Assistant in Urban Metabolism, Ben-Gurion University of the Negev.

- Using data to create information systems with MATLAB programming language.

- Performs statistical analysis of urban consumption and waste generation in Tel Aviv.

2019-2020: Private tutor in "Databases" course - SQL language, teaching the construction and

management of databases.

2018-2020: Private tutor in "Introduction to Java Programming" course – Aiding students with

their programming studies.

### **Projects**

Facebook Israel Virtual Hackathon 2020

#### **Volunteering**

2004-2012: "Scouts" youth movement member at "Aviv" tribe – counseling for a year in "Beit

HaYeled" boarding school in Tel Aviv and instructing children with special needs.

2001-2012: Member of Israel's National Team in gymnastics and acrobatics – Representing

Israel in European and World Championships.

# **Military Service**

2013-2015: Combat Fitness Instructor, School for Commander and Infantry, Israel Defense Forces.

#### Languages

Hebrew – Native Speaker. English – Very High Proficiency.